//make array of questions.
var questions = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer: "HyperText Markup Language",
        options: [
            "HighText Machine Language",
            "HyperText and links Markup Language",
            "HyperText Markup Language",
            "None of these"   
         ]
    },
       
    {
        num: 2,
        question: "What CSS property is used to specify the transparency of an element?",
        answer: "opacity",
        options: [
            "visibility",
            "transparancy",
            "opacity",
            "None of these"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 3,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a JavaSript keyword to declare variables ?",
        answer: "decl",
        options: [
            "let",
            "var",
            "decl",
            "const"   
                    ]
     },


     {

        num: 4,
        question: "What is concatenation?",
        answer: "combining strings",
        options: [
            "combining strings",
            "storing strings",
            "separating strings",
            "printing out strings"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 5,
        question: "What is the property in CSS used to change the background color of an element?",
        answer: "background-color",
        options: [
            "background-color",
            "bgcolor",
            "color",
            "All of these"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 6,
        question: "In Java, what does API stand for?",
        answer:"Applied Protocols Interface",
        
        options: [
            "Applied Protocols Interface",
            "Application Production Increments",
            "Arrays Producing Iterations",
            "None of these"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 7,
        question: "Which is the correct way to comment out something in HTML?",
        answer: "None of these",
        options: [
            "Using ## and #",
            "Using [-- and --]",
            "Using *-- and --*",
            "None of these"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 8,
        question: "Which of the following is not a “primitive data” type?",
        answer: "function",
        options: [
            "boolean",
            "int",
            "char",
            "function"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 9,
        question: "What is the CSS property used to make the rounded borders or corners around an element?",
        answer: "border-radius",
        options: [
            "border-collapse",
            "border-radius",
            "border-spacing",
            "None of these"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 10,
        question: "In java script, what does json stand for?",
        answer: "Java Script Object",
        options: [
            "Java Sign Number",
            "Java Object Numerical",
            "Java Script Object",
            "None of these"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 11,
        question: "What is the correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage?",
        answer: "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
        options: [
            "Head, Title, HTML, Body",
            "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
            "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
            "Body, HTML, Head, Title"   
                    ]
     },

     {
        num: 12,
        question: "What does CSS stands for?",
        answer: "Cascading style sheets",
        options: [
            "Cascade style sheets",
            "Color and style sheets",
            "Cascading style sheets",
            "None of these"   
                    ]
     },
    ];




